Jaime Balmes 62 Int. 1301 Polanco CP 11510 Mexico DF Cell.: +52 1 5545663228

joseguadarramaf@yahoo.es

### **Summary**

Finance professional with experience in: Debt and FX Markets, Equity Trading, Mutual funds, ETF's, Asset/Investment Management, Accounting and Fiscal Consultant. Interested in: Hedge Funds, Equity Trading, Fixed Income and FX Trading, Global Markets, Derivatives, Investment Management, Private Banking and Sales.

#### Work Experience

# JC Consulting Group <u>www.grupojc.com.mx</u>

## **Corporate Sales Director**

Mexico City, Mexico Feb 2013 – Currently

- Manage and expand base of clients in Mexico City, Guadalajara and Queretaro.
- Responsible for the overall achievement of company's sales goals.
- Manage company's sales force, projecting annual sales, tracking sales performance, and interacting with other areas of the company to ensure the business orders are correctly executed.

# RILSA <u>www.dineroalacarta.mx</u>

CEO

Mexico City, Mexico Sep 2012 – Currently

- In charge of the entire management organization nationwide.
- Set annual budget, investment planning and implementation.
- In charge of fund raising with investors (AUM 10 MM USD in 3 months), and keeping a way to find more potential investors.
- Build and manage investment funds in such areas as home building and parking lots, towards an initial public offering of 2 REIT's. AUM 20 MM USD per year.

## Scotiabank Casa de Bolsa www.scotiabank.com.mx

### Private Banker / Asset Manager

Mexico City, Mexico Jun 2011 – Sep 2012

- Manage and expand the base of clients.
- Investment and brokerage client management.
- Trading of equity, debt, funds, ETF's
- Advising in investment strategies

#### Santander Casa de Bolsa www.santander.com.mx

# **Private Banker / Asset Manager**

Mexico City, Mexico April 2007- March 2011

- As a Private Banker; managed and expanded the base of clients, AUM: \$75 MM USD
- Planned, structured and developed the investment strategies for clients
- Portafolio Management
- Managed a small equity fund \$10MM USD

### Invex Casa de Bolsa www.invex.com

## **Private Banker**

Mexico City, Mexico Dec 2005 – April 2007

- Manage current clients
- Expand base of clients

## **DuPont www.dupont.com**

### **Sales Manager**

Mexico City, Mexico
June 2005 – Dec 2005

· Review customers for authorize credit, based on its liquidity and debt

#### **Education**

Universidad de Cantabria Business School

Santander, Spain & Mexico City, Mexico

Master Internacional en Banca y Mercados Financieros

Sep 2006 - Feb 2008

**Universidad Anahuac Business School** 

**BS International Business** 

Mexico City, Mexico Nov 2005

### **Other Studies & Certifications**

- Asesor en Estrategias de Inversion Asociacion Mexicana de Intermediarios Bursatiles Mexico City
- Fluent in English and Spanish
- Experience in software such as Bloomberg Professional, Reuters Financial Software, and SAP.

### Other Related Experience & Interests

- Raced over fifteen 10km races
- One half marathon
- Training for the Chicago Marathon Oct. 2013